IN THE VAST
DARKNESS OF SPACE,
A PAIR OF
GLOWING EYES STARE
DOWN AT THE
EARTH. A CELESTIAL
BEING WATCHING.
DOWN BELOW,
THE SKY ITSELF
SHOWS THOSE EYES.
PEOPLE SCREAM AND
RUN IN PANIC,
EXCEPT ONE MAN
STANDING CALM IN
THE MIDDLE OF
THE STREET,
HOLDING HIS PLASTIC
BAG. THEN A
STRANGER APPEARS ON
EVERY SCREEN.
HE SAYS HE
WILL HANDLE IT.
HE STANDS ON
THE PEAK OF
MOUNT EVEREST,
PREPARING HIS ATTACK.
HE CALLS FOR
HIS PARTNER.
SHE'S A GIANT
WOMAN, 10,000 METERS
TALL. AFTER YEARS
OF NEVER BEING
SEEN, SHE FINALLY
SHOWS HERSELF.
THE HEAT OF
THE EARTH IS
BECOMING UNBEARABLE,
AND SHE WANTS
TO END THIS
QUICKLY. HE RAISES
A HANDFUL OF
GLOWING ORBS,
READY TO THROW
THEM. THEIR PURPOSE
IS TO GRANT
HER POWER.
THE ORBS BEGIN
LINKING WITH HER.
ONE ATTACHES TO
HER WRIST,
FORMING ARMOR AND
A WEAPON AROUND
HER. SHE LAUNCHES
HERSELF INTO THE
SKY, CHARGING STRAIGHT
FOR THE CELESTIAL
BEING. DOWN BELOW,
HER PARTNER WATCHES,
ASTONISHED. THEN A
FINGER PIERCES THROUGH
THE SKY.
IT IS MANY
TIMES LARGER THAN
THE GIANT WOMAN
HERSELF. IT WAS
AS SIMPLE AS
CRUSHING AN ANT.
THE MAN WITH
THE BAG CAN
ONLY STARE.
HIS BAG SLIPS
FROM HIS HAND
AS THE FINGER
COMES DOWN TOWARD
HIM. HE WHISPERS
A NAME,
"AMBER LOCKHART?" THE
GIRL HE REMEMBERS,
THE ONE WHO
LOOKS JUST LIKE
THE CELESTIAL BEING.
AND THEN THE
EARTH WAS GONE.
SUDDENLY, TIME REWINDS
THREE YEARS BACK
INSIDE A CLASSROOM
IN THE MIDDLE
OF A LESSON.
THE MAN WITH
THE BAG IS
AWAKE. HE HAS
REGRESSED. HE GOES
PEEKING TO ANOTHER
CLASSROOM AND SEES
HER, AMBER LOCKHART.
PERFECT GRADES,
NOTHING IS EVER
A CHALLENGE FOR
HER, BUT SHE
SITS ALONE,
ALWAYS A LONER.
HE CAN'T UNDERSTAND
IT. WHAT COULD
MAKE SOMEONE LIKE
HER DESTROY THE
EARTH? BUT IF
THE FUTURE CAN
BE CHANGED,
HE'S GOING TO
FIND OUT.